Joseph Costa Papers
Joseph Costa Papers
1946-1967
Costa, Joseph.
95 linear ft.
Papers of the American photographer, founder of the National Press Photographers Association, executive editor of the National press photographer. Died 1988. Most of the material relates to the National Press Photographers Association, including minutes, financial and other administrative records; a run of the National press photographer (1956-1967); photographs of various subjects, including some of Costa's work (Eastman Kodak Company, Famous Photographers School, King Features Syndicate, Trans World Airlines); family photographs; and writings by and about Costa. Approximately 9 linear feet of material pertains to the camera-in-the-courtroom controversy. Correspondence includes that of National Press Photographers Association officers John W. Ahlhauser, James Bennet, Morris S. Berman, Joseph Costa, John Faber, and Arthur Witman; and organizations including American Judicature Society, American Medical Association, American Newspaper Publishers Association, American Press Institute, American Red Cross, American Society of Magazine Photographers, American Society of Newspaper Editors, American Standards Association, Associated Press, Cigar Institute of America, Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., and Eastman Kodak Company.
148907
Biographical History
Joseph Costa was a veteran newspaper photographer whose career spanned 60 years. For nearly 44 years he was photographer, chief photographer, or photo supervisor on the New York Morning World, New York Morning News, the New York Daily News, the New York Daily Mirror, and King Features Syndicate. Until 1985, he taught photojournalism at Ball State University, which awarded him an honorary degree when he retired.
One of Mr. Costa's main interests was freedom of Information. To make courtroom photography possible, he worked on a technical education program for photographers, demonstrations before lawyers and judges, and a respectable and responsible image for the press photographer. He is frequently introduced before his articles as "Mr. Press Photography." In one of his articles on freedom of the press, he states:
The proper dissemination of news by a free press is not accomplished solely by the printed word. There is a visual record, too, that must be transmitted to do the complete job. The object of this complete job, of course, is the informed public on which our democracy stands.
He was a founder, first president, and chairman of the board of the National Press Photographers Association and executive editor or the official NPPA magazine, National Press Photographer, from 1946 to 1966. The NPPA's Joseph Costa Award and its Joseph Costa Award for Courtroom Photography are named in his honor.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Joseph Costa Papers consists primarily of material relating to the National Press Photographers Association (NPPA), and reflects Costa's intense dedication to advancing freedom of information and freedom of the press, particularly in the courtroom. Subject files is divided into three subseries: general business topics, National Press Photographers Association, and personal material. The NPPA material covers the full range of the organization's operations, including correspondence, conventions, publicity, membership, awards, insurance, and more. Photographs contains business, NPPA, and personal. Published material contains articles about Costa, clippings, page proofs, a few photographs by Costa, pamphlets and other printed material. Writings comprises books, articles, speeches, and approximately twenty years' worth of the NPPA's trade magazine, National Press Photographer, during Costa's tenure as editor. Audio-visual material contains a filmstrip on Famous Photographers School and six items related to the NPPA in a variety of formats (newsreels, movies and tapes).
Arrangement of the Collection
Folders are arranged alphabetically within series and subseries.
Subject and Genre Headings
Photography; Ahlhauser, John W.; Bennet, James.; Berman, Morris S. (Morris Stanley); Costa, Joseph.; Faber, John, 1918-1993.; Witman, Arthur, 1902-1991.; American Judicature Society.; American Medical Association.; American Newspaper Publishers Association.; American Press Institute.; American Red Cross.; American Society of Magazine Photographers.; American Society of Newspaper Editors.; American Standards Association.; Associated Press.; Cigar Institute of America.; Columbia Broadcasting System, inc.; Eastman Kodak Company.; King Features Syndicate.; National Press Photographers Association (U.S.); Trans World Airlines.; Famous Photographers School.; National press photographer.; Courtroom art.; Crime and the press.; Free press and fair trial.; Freedom of information.; Freedom of the press.; Journalism, Pictorial.; Photojournalists.; Photojournalists, Education.; Newspaper court reporting.; Photographers -- United States.; Photojournalism -- United States.; Television broadcasting of court proceedings -- United States.; Annual reports.; Articles.; Awards.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Financial records.; Negatives (photographs); Photographs.; Receipts (financial records); Slides (photographs); Photographers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Joseph Costa, 1967-1985.
Inventory
- Subject files
  - Business
    - Actor and Actress Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Biography (Box 1)
    - Equipment, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - European Trip (Box 1)
    - Florida Assignment (Box 1)
    - Future Activities (Box 1)
    - King Features Syndicate
      - 1948-1952, 4 folders (Box 1)
      - 1955-1961, 6 folders (Box 1)
      - 1963 (Box 1)
      - Captions (Box 1)
      - Expense Account (Box 1)
      - History of New York Sunday Mirror (Box 1)
      - Morton, Hugh (Box 1)
      - New Studio (Box 1)
      - Photography Column (Box 1)
      - Photographic Equipment, 1956-1962; 4 folders (Box 1)
      - Sarno, Richard (Box 1)
      - Work Schedule (Box 1)
    - Industrial Photographers (Box 1)
    - Kling Photo Corporation (Box 1)
    - Kodak (Box 1)
    - Models Pictures (Box 1)
    - Pamphlet: Beginner's Guide to Color Photography (Box 1)
    - Photographic Society of America (Box 1)
    - Popular Photography (Box 1)
    - Roosevelt Raceway (Box 1)
    - The Silurian Society, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Sylvania Special Projects (Box 2)
    - Television Show (Box 2)
    - Town and Country magazine (Box 2)
    - Trans World Airlines (Box 2)
    - Trolley Cars (Box 2)
    - General, 1967; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - National Press Photographers Association (N.P.P.A,)
    - Administration
      - General (Box 2)
      - Regional Plan (Box 2)
      - National Officers
        - General (Box 2)
        - Board of Directors Decisions (Box 2)
        - Abbott, Gene (Box 2)
        - Ahlhauser, John (Box 2)
        - Atkins, Ollie (Box 2)
        - Bennett, James, 3 folders (Box 2)
        - Bennetti, Joseph (Box 2)
        - Berman, Morris (Box 2)
        - Boyd, Robert (Box 2)
        - Cooper, Charles, 4 folders (Box 2)
        - Costa, Joseph (Box 2)
        - Dussinger, Marshall, 4 folders (Box 2)
        - East, Robert (Box 2)
        - Faber, John, 3 folders (Box 2)
        - Hammersley, Howard (Box 2)
        - Higgins, Charles (Box 2)
        - Lawes, Bayard, 2 folders (Box 2)
        - Linck, Lester, 2 folders (Box 2)
        - Linck, Lester, 3 folders (Box 3)
        - Mack, Charles, 3 folders (Box 3)
        - McCall, Floyd (Box 3)
        - McLaughlin, Kenneth (Box 3)
        - Mellor, Sam (Box 3)
        - Olson, Cal, 3 folders (Box 3)
        - Rammel, John, 2 folders (Box 3)
        - Richmond, Marvin, 2 folders (Box 3)
        - Swenson, Don, 3 folders (Box 3)
        - Swenson, Leslie, 6 folders (Box 3)
        - Threlfall, Paul (Box 3)
        - Tiffany, Nelson, 3 folders (Box 3)
        - Witman, Arthur, 9 folders (Box 4)
    - Air Conditioner Papers (Box 4)
    - American Council for Education in Journalism, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - American Judicature Society (Box 4)
    - American Medical Association, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - American Museum of Photography (Box 4)
    - American Newspapers Publishers Association, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - American Press Institute, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - American Red Cross (Box 4)
    - American Society of Magazine Photographers (Box 4)
    - American Society of Newspaper Editors, 4 folders (Box 4)
    - American Standards Association (Box 4)
    - Annual reports, 1947-1954; 1956-1963; 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Annual [Yearbook], 1948-1949; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Associated Press (Box 4)
    - Associated Press Managing Editors (Box 4)
    - Audio Visual (Box 4)
    - Biographical Material, 2 folders (Box 4, 5)
    - Blood (Box 5)
    - Boston Globe Insult (Box 5)
    - Camera Magazine (Box 5)
    - The Camera (Box 5)
    - Cigar Institute, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Chapters Program, 10 folders (Box 5)
    - Color Corporation of America (Box 5)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Committees
      - 1949, 1954, 1957-1959, 5 folders (Box 5)
      - Audio Visual
        - 1953-1955, 1956-1958, 2 folders (Box 5)
        - Library, 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Credentials (Box 5)
      - Education
        - General, 6 folders (Box 5)
        - 1948-1950 (Box 5)
        - 1956, 1959, 1961-1964, 3 folders (Box 6)
      - Education and Technical
        - General (Box 6)
        - 1955 (Box 6)
        - Policy Discussions, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Executive, 1956; 1960,; 1963-1966; 5 folders (Box 6)
      - Honorary Recognitions, 1951-1965; 11 folders (Box 6)
      - Joint Media
        - 1964, 1965, 1968, 3 folders (Box 6)
        - Pamphlet (Box 6)
      - Legislative, 3 folders (Box 6)
      - Liaison (Box 6)
      - Newsreel-Television (Box 6)
      - Nominations
        - 1948, 1950, 2 folders (Box 6)
        - 1952, 1954-1956, 1958, 1959, 1966, 7 folders (Box 7)
      - Police-Fire-Press, 7 folders (Box 7)
      - Public Relations (Box 7)
      - Redistricting (Box 7)
      - Regional (Box 7)
      - Regional Publications (Box 7)
      - Reinstatement (Box 7)
      - Resolutions (Box 7)
      - Sports, 4 folders (Box 7)
      - Study, 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Television (Box 7)
    - Constitution, 7 folders (Box 7)
    - Contest
      - Award certificate (Oversize 7)
      - Clippings, 5 folders (Box 7, 8)
      - Photo
        - Awards (Box 8)
        - Encyclopedia Britannica, 12 folders (Box 8)
        - Fifty Great Newspictures (Box 8)
        - Graflex (Box 8)
        - Look Magazine (Box 8)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
        - National Fire Protection Association (Box 8)
        - Newspictures of the Year 1949, 1957, 1964-1967, 6 folders (Box 8)
        - People to People Program (Box 9)
        - Photographer of the Year, 2 folders (Box 9)
        - Rawlings Sporting Goods (Box 9)
        - Rating Slips (Box 9)
        - The Toni Company (Box 9)
        - Traveling Exhibit, 4 folders (Box 9)
        - TV-Newsreel, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Conventions
      - 1947 (Box 9)
      - 1948-1949 (Box 9)
      - 1949-1950 (Box 9)
      - 1950 (Box 9)
      - 1951 (Box 9)
      - 1952 (Box 9)
      - 1953
        - Clippings (Box 9)
        - General (Box 9)
        - Queen Pageant (Box 9)
      - 1954 (Box 9)
      - 1955
        - General, 2 folders (Box 9)
        - Queen Pageant (Box 9)
        - Sites (Box 9)
      - 1956
        - Clippings (Oversize 1)
        - General, 4 folders (Box 9, 10)
        - Housing (Box 10)
        - Queen Pageant (Box 10)
      - 1957
        - Clippings (Oversize 2)
        - General, 5 folders (Box 10)
        - Housing (Box 10)
        - Queen Pageant (Box 10)
        - Sites (Box 10)
      - 1958
        - General (Box 10)
        - Queen Pageant (Box 10)
      - 1959
        - General, 4 folders (Box 10, 11)
        - Queen Pageant, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Sites, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - 1960
        - Agenda (Box 11)
        - General, 3 folders (Box 11)
        - Queen Pageant (Box 11)
        - Site (Box 11)
      - 1961
        - General, 3 folders (Box 11)
        - Manufacturer's Exhibit (Box 11)
        - Queen Pageant (Box 11)
        - Sites, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - 1962
        - American Face Pageant (Box 11)
      - 1963
        - General (Box 11)
        - American Face Pageant (Box 11)
      - 1964
        - General (Box 11)
        - American Face Pageant, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - 1965 (Box 12)
      - 1966 (Box 12)
      - 1967 (Box 12)
      - 1969 (Box 12)
      - American Face Pageant, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Beauty Contest Winners (Box 12)
      - International Beauty Congress (Box 12)
      - Programs (Box 12)
      - Publicity (Box 12)
      - Minutes and Annual Reports
        - 1946-1950, 9 folders (Box 12)
        - 1950-1956, 17 folders (Box 13)
        - 1956-1960, 17 folders (Box 14)
        - 1961-1966, 10 folders (Box 15)
      - Banquet menu (Oversize 3)
    - Correspondence
      - Costa
        - 1946-1950, 11 folders (Box 15)
        - 1951-1963, 18 folders (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 16)
      - National
        - 1948-1950, 7 folders (Box 16, 17)
        - 1949-1952, 19 folders (Box 17)
        - 1950-1958, 21 folders (Box 18)
        - 1960-1963, 11 folders (Box 19)
      - Regional
        - 1947, No. 6, 3 folders (Box 19)
        - 1948, No. 6, 3 folders (Box 19)
        - 1948-1950, No. 6 (Box 19)
        - 1948-1950, No.s 7, 8, 9, 5 folders (Box 20)
        - 1948-1952, No. 5, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - 1950-1951, No. 6, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - 1950-1955, No.s 2, 7, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - 1951, No. 3 (Box 20)
        - 1951-1952, No. 10 (Box 20)
        - 1951-1955, No.s 1, 4, 5, 6, 6 folders (Box 20)
        - 1951-1955, No.s 8, 9, 2 folders (Box 21)
        - 1952-1957, No. 2 (Box 21)
        - 1953, No. 6 (Box 21)
        - 1953-1954, No.s 2, 3, 2 folders (Box 21)
        - 1953-1954, No.s 3, 6, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - 1953-1955, No. 10 (Box 22)
        - 1954, No. 3 (Box 22)
        - 1954-1955, No.s 5, 6, 7, 8, 10, 8 folders (Box 22)
        - 1954-1956, No. 10 (Box 22)
        - 1954-1957, No.s 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 9 folders (Box 22)
        - 1955, No. 1 (Box 22)
        - 1955, No.s 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 9, 10, 13 folders (Box 23)
        - 1955-1956, No. 3 (Box 23)
        - 1955-1957, No. 9, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - 1956, No.s 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 9 folders (Box 23)
        - 1956, No.s 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 5 folders (Box 24)
        - 1956-1957, No.s 1, 2, 6, 3 folders (Box 24)
        - 1957, No. 8 (Box 24)
        - 1957-1958, No.s 1, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 9, 10, 14 folders (Box 24)
        - 1957-1959, No. 6, 2 folders (Box 24)
        - 1958, No. 10 (Box 24)
        - 1958-1959, No. 9 (Box 24)
        - 1959-1960, No.s 1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 5 folders (Box 25)
        - 1959-1961, No. 3 (Box 25)
        - 1960, No. 6, 3 folders (Box 25)
        - 1960-1961, No. 6, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - 1961, No. 6 (Box 25)
        - 1961-1962, No. 6, 2 folders (Box 26)
        - 1962, No. 6, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Cormac Chemical Corporation (Box 26)
    - Copyrighting Photographs (Box 26)
    - Credentials
      - Civil Defense, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - General (Box 26)
      - License Plates (Box 26)
      - Phony (Box 26)
      - Portrait Photographers, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Privileges (Box 26)
    - Drafting of Photographers (Box 26)
    - Eastman Kodak Company, 9 folders (Box 26)
    - Editor and Publisher (Box 26)
    - Editors (Box 26)
    - Education
      - Audio Visual (Box 26)
      - Colleges
        - American Press Institutes, 2 folders (Box 26)
        - East Texas State College (Box 26)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 26)
        - Research Papers (Box 26)
      - Fraternities
        - Sigma Delta Chi (Box 26)
        - Kappa Alpha Mu, 3 folders (Box 27)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Individuals
        - Dr. Edgerton (Box 27)
        - Prof. Edom (Box 27)
        - Vincent S. Jones (Box 27)
      - Photo Conference
        - Michigan (Box 27)
        - Rochester
          - 1953, 1957, 13 folders (Box 27)
          - 1962, 3 folders (Box 28)
      - Short Course
        - Correspondence, 1963-1966; 4 folders (Box 28)
        - Air Force, 2 folders (Box 28)
        - Chicago, 2 folders (Box 28)
        - Cross Country, 1958-1960; 3 folders (Box 28)
        - Florida (Box 28)
        - Minnesota (Box 28)
        - New England (Box 28)
        - West Coast, 1953-1957; 7 folders (Box 28)
        - Host
          - Kent State University, 1946-1956; 8 folders (Box 29)
          - Syracuse University (Box 29)
          - Texas A and M (Box 29)
          - University of Illinois (Box 29)
          - University of Kansas, 2 folders (Box 29)
          - University of Miami (Box 29)
          - University of Minnesota (Box 29)
          - University of Missouri, 4 folders (Box 29)
          - University of North Carolina, 3 folders (Box 29)
          - University of Western Ontario (Box 29)
        - General, 3 folders (Box 29)
        - Operation (Box 29)
      - Student Affiliates, 3 folders (Box 30)
      - Survey
        - Bowling Green State University (Box 30)
        - Penn State University (Box 30)
        - Southern Illinois University (Box 30)
      - TV-Newsfilm Workshop, 1963-1967; 5 folders (Box 30)
    - Elections, 1948-1960; 9 folders (Box 30)
    - Employees (Box 30)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Engraver's plates (Box 85)
    - Ephemera (Box 85)
    - Ethics (Box 30)
    - Expositions
      - Photography in the Fine Arts (Box 30)
      - Washington, 1957; 3 folders (Box 30, 31)
    - Field Enterprises, 1963; 1965; 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Financial
      - Accounts, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Audits (Box 31)
      - Bank Statements, Bills and Checks
        - July, 1945-March 1950, 26 folders (Box 31)
        - April 1950-May 1950, 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Bills Paid (Box 32)
      - Checkbook, 1948; 1953 (Oversize 3)
      - Check Stubs (Box 32)
      - Expense Account (Box 32)
      - Internal Revenue Department (Box 32)
      - Ledger
        - 1945-1952, 7 folders (Box 32)
        - 1948 (Oversize 3)
      - National City Bank (Box 32)
      - Passbooks (Box 32)
      - Problems (Box 32)
      - Statement, 1954 (Oversize 3)
      - Treasurer's Reports
        - 1946: National (Box 32)
        - 1947: National, Regional, 2 folders (Box 32)
        - 1948: National (Box 32)
        - 1949: National, Regional, 2 folders (Box 32)
        - 1950: Regional (Box 32)
        - 1951: National (Box 32)
    - Foreign Organizations, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Freedom of Information (F.O.I.)
      See also Photographs: NPPA: FOI and Audio-visual: NPPA: FOI
      - Canon 35
        - American Bar Association
          - Convention
            - General, 3 folders (Box 32)
            - Los Angeles, 3 folders (Box 32)
            - New Orleans, 2 folders (Box 32)
            - Calendars and Codes (Box 33)
          - Demonstration
            - New York (Box 33)
            - Philadelphia, 2 folders (Box 33)
            - Texas (Box 33)
          - General (Box 33)
          - Study Committee, 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Articles
          - Published
            - By Costa, 2 folders (Box 33)
            - Edited by Costa (Box 33)
            - Others, 6 folders (Box 33)
          - Typescripts (Box 33)
        - Clippings, 6 folders (Box 33, 34)
        - Correspondence
          - American Bar Association (Box 34)
          - American Judicature Society (Box 34)
          - American Society of Newspaper Editors (Box 34)
          - Brookings' Study (Box 34)
          - Kent Cooper (Box 34)
          - Executive Committee (Box 34)
          - Federal Judicial Council (Box 34)
          - Percy Foreman (Box 34)
          - Al M. Heck (Box 34)
          - Fred M. Mazzulla, Esq. (Box 34)
          - Charles R. McCain (Box 34)
          - Robert McCaudless (Box 34)
          - C.A. Morris, 2 folders (Box 34)
          - National Association of Broadcasters (Box 34)
          - Newsday, L.I. (Box 34)
          - Pennsylvania Ban in the Courts (Box 34)
          - Inez Robb Letter (Box 34)
          - United Press International (Box 34)
          - 1957, 2 folders (Box 34)
          - 1958, 4 folders (Box 34)
          - 1962 (Box 34)
          - General (Box 34)
        - Court Cases
          - Atlanta Appeal (Box 34)
          - Billy Sol Estes (Box 34)
          - Kravitz (Box 34)
          - Connie Nicholas (Box 34)
          - Jack Ruby (Box 34)
          - Shrunk (Box 34)
          - Westmoreland County (Box 34)
        - Court Documents
          - Backgrounder (Box 35)
          - Briefs, 2 folders (Box 35)
          - Exhibit (Box 35)
          - Miscellaneous Dockets (Box 35)
          - Opinions (Box 35)
          - Transcripts, 2 folders (Box 35)
        - Courtroom Presentations
          - General (Box 36)
          - Colorado Hearings, 6 folders (Box 36)
          - Courtroom Coverage (Box 36)
          - Rules for Courtroom Coverage, 2 folders (Box 36)
          - Moot Court Demonstrations (Box 36)
        - Editorial Rebuttals, 2 folders (Box 36)
        - General
          - 1946-1961, 7 folders (Box 36)
          - 1946-1958, 18 folders (Box 37)
          - 1958-1959, 6 folders (Box 38)
          - National Association of Municipal Judges (Box 38)
          - National Association of Compensation Claims Attorneys (Box 38)
          - Colorado Courts (Box 38)
        - Historical Background (Box 38)
        - Honor Roll of Judges, 3 folders (Box 38)
        - Judges
          - Leo Freund (Box 38)
          - Charles Gilbert (Box 38)
          - Frank H. Hall (Box 38)
          - Al M. Heck (Box 38)
          - Walter B. Jones (Box 38)
          - Harold R. Medina (Box 38)
        - Mimeographed Letters, 6 folders (Box 38)
        - Miscellaneous, A-Z, 27 folders (Box 38)
        - Pamphlets, 3 folders (Box 39)
        - Press Releases (Box 39)
        - Proposals and Reports, 5 folders (Box 39)
        - Research Papers, 8 folders (Box 39, 40)
        - Statements and Speeches, 12 folders (Box 40)
        - Survey (Box 40)
        - TV Editorials (Box 40)
      - General
        - Missouri Center
          - General (Box 40)
          - 1959-1967, 6 folders (Box 40)
          - Bulletins, 8 folders (Box 40, 41)
          - Speeches (Box 41)
          - Seminar (Box 41)
        - Clippings, 2 folders (Box 41)
        - Committee
          - 1952-1957, 5 folders (Box 41)
          - 1958-1959, 1962-1966, 7 folders (Box 42)
        - Individuals
          - Corn (Box 42)
          - Freier, 2 folders (Box 42)
          - Rogers (Box 42)
          - Wiggins (Box 42)
      - Legislation
        - Attacks on Photographers
          - 1949, 1951-1959, 1962, 1964, 13 folders (Box 42)
          - California (Box 42)
          - California and Florida (Box 42)
          - Gugel Gase (Box 42)
          - Milledge Incident (Box 42)
          - Redbook magazine (Box 42)
          - American Photography magazine (Box 43)
        - California (Box 43)
        - Federal Public Records Law, 3 folders (Box 43)
        - John Moss Government Information Subcommittee (Box 43)
        - House Bill H.R. 1017 (Box 43)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 43)
        - Wisconsin Criminal Code (Box 43)
      - Military
        - General (Box 43)
        - Public Information Office (P.I.O.)
          - Air Force, 3 folders (Box 43)
          - Navy (Box 43)
      - Policies
        - General Services Administration (Box 43)
        - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 43)